{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"664d8de3-d837-433d-b2f7-984a510bdb60"},"exam":{"id":"0a0f46b4-4a03-4d02-a4e8-49607dcee9f1","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"32c7f1bb-425d-4d33-b870-b88f89ef9f08","domain":"security","question":"An oil and gas utility company which is highly regulated must create a cloud governance scheme. The company is organized into multiple autonomous departments which will all be using AWS resources. These departments each sponsor independent projects that are reviewed by regulatory boards for the approval of customer price increases. The code and infrastructure for each project has production, development, and testing environments. Which of the following account strategies will maximize security and operational efficiency for the company?","explanation":"A multi-layered account structure will work best for this company, leveraging AWS Organizations to establish Organizational Units for each department, and separate production, development, and testing environments. While there is no physical AWS account at the department level, Service Control Policies can be applied at the Organizational Unit level, and billing can be reported separately for each department. An account for each department, in which the department combines dev/test/and prod, or a single account for the company hosting all workloads together will NOT provide for segregation of production, development, and testing environments at the account level. Multiple standalone accounts for each department and environment would compromise operational efficiency in managing environments across departments as there is no overarching AWS Organization to manage all the accounts centrally.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/Security/AWS_Security_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"AWS Security Best Practices"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/organizations/","title":"AWS Organizations"}],"answers":[{"id":"e4be6081f1a5dc1cc67c1a4633121580","text":"Create an Organization Unit structure in AWS Organizations with separate underlying accounts for production, development, and testing environments","correct":true},{"id":"6773420477c1653d8837f13bfa8ec24d","text":"Create a single AWS account for centralized security management","correct":false},{"id":"bb38e2c475c21f60a71674d4dd27ff93","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for each autonomous department within the company","correct":false},{"id":"281f961ca6e4d83f6570979548ba64e2","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for the production environment, one for the development environment, and one for the testing environment for all departments","correct":false}]},{"id":"2d6841a4-2163-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS, you can stop or terminate instances when not in use. Which of the following concepts describes this capability?","explanation":"Elasticity denotes the ability to increase or reduce the number or capabilities of AWS resources when needed. In this case, stopping or terminating instances means that you are reducing the number of AWS resources used in your environment.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"857defc5b4c6f1fef867a03c300bdd29","text":"Loose Coupling","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true}]},{"id":"i24lu8u9-bdxm-hnxr-9xkq-ogorvl1cou1f","domain":"tech","question":"In which of the following is CloudFront content cached?","explanation":"Edge Locations consist of over 200+ points of presence around the world which provide fast entry into Amazon's global network. Because of how widespread they are, users can connect to their nearest Edge Location, and have their traffic sent through Amazon's fast Global Network to reach the resources it needs sooner. This is how CloudFront's caching mechanism works. There are far less Availability Zones and Regions than Edge Locations, which is why CloudFront does not use them for caching content.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"About CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"47df2b78ac4b3edfbf1c6d0b2a64c579","text":"Data Center","correct":false},{"id":"f447ac856e7e72435904956e3b15f433","text":"Region","correct":false},{"id":"e95464b98c902ebad35546ca12a620a4","text":"Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"ec50121a3fdd0fb561e14291a5741b6e","text":"Edge Location","correct":true}]},{"id":"ee56fwac-hgmj-xrxe-1u42-pucfbmasuhh1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is not a compute service?","explanation":"Elastic Block Store is a storage service - all others are compute services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/compute/","title":"AWS Compute"}],"answers":[{"id":"34bc95906489c2d5c9583e3230cd48b2","text":"Elastic Block Store","correct":true},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"e915ef52-2be6-4fba-8d62-b668f639c29a","domain":"billing","question":"To stay within the AWS Free Tier using Amazon EC2 for the first 12 months of having an AWS account, which of the following instance types should you use?","explanation":"One of the EC2 requirements for staying within the AWS Free Tier is using EC2 micro instances only. While the other instance types can be cheap, only t2.micro is eligibile for free tier usage","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"05c25e549fbb3f158f12a9945bff38ee","text":"t3.medium","correct":false},{"id":"ab61127647912c159c3fc08e9a102efc","text":"t2.small","correct":false},{"id":"cc114cafeb511c9cbe6666312f54a8de","text":"m5.medium","correct":false},{"id":"1d4f2c610dbeb44e7ba09fed19564c76","text":"t2.micro","correct":true}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true}]},{"id":"eaf197bf-a9f1-4611-90be-dbcf7364c74a","domain":"concepts","question":"You have an application load balancer for routing traffic from developers to the EC2 instance that contains a web application being put into operation. To prepare for the application going live for public use, you add an Auto Scaling Group and a second application load balancer to route web traffic from customers to the EC2 instance. The addition is an example of which of the following:","explanation":"This is an example of scalability, which means that systems are expected to grow over time with no drop in performance. ","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2166e76dc88d642260416a536b06a412","text":"Durability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"820b8f74ad843d1574106ec4cadfc07e","text":"Reliability","correct":false}]},{"id":"f119625a-2f3b-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your Project Manager needs to know the daily spend of the companyâ€™s AWS account over the last 60 days to consider creating and implementing cost-effective measures. What should you do?","explanation":"Cost Explorer provides a trio of preconfigured views designed to quickly get you to common spends in your AWS environment. For viewing the daily spend over the last 60 days, your Project Manager needs to click the 'Daily Spend View' link. AWS Budgets is for generating automatic alerts when your AWS costs or usage exceed, or are forecasted to exceed, the thresholds you set; it is not for tracking your spend.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-what-is.html","title":"What Is AWS Billing and Cost Management?"}],"answers":[{"id":"ae4dff5b9f90f7f36261f1743d9c6eb1","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Linked Account View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"3061bd4594121d528b00ebc0b3cabd8b","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Service View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"e3963c15d2d033b249d8f75f4b7c05ff","text":"Direct him to AWS Budgets.","correct":false},{"id":"224e965acad73b5fc7fd31b503e947db","text":"Direct him to Daily Spend View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":true}]},{"id":"1bq7soel-r0fa-9nu9-nkn7-tsl4tdqsb4ne","domain":"security","question":"You would like to give an application running on one of your EC2 instances access to an S3 bucket - what is the best way to implement this?","explanation":"The recommended method to assign permissions to apps running in EC2 is to use IAM roles. Making the bucket public could work, but will also expose all the data to the internet and is not secure. The other methods are also less secure than using IAM roles and are not recommended in this case.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","title":"IAM Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"6d5604611f5103e032eae843cc2d3861","text":"Give the application a set of Access Keys","correct":false},{"id":"506f9dca07627c4a0037801fd015ae25","text":"Use an IAM user for the application","correct":false},{"id":"200bfcc1caf00feb47c6ca792e965a17","text":"Make the bucket public","correct":false},{"id":"1e3f1e527016bc7fae2856f9acfd533a","text":"Assign the instance an IAM role","correct":true}]},{"id":"rbmak3ks-m1is-jjm6-oc1s-77yv6l2wutv1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below methods can you use to interact with Glacier?.","explanation":"You can interact with Glacier using the RESTful Glacier web service, the Java or .NET SDKs, or by using Amazon S3 Lifecycle Policies. CloudFormation control of Glacier is currently limited to invoking Lifecycle Policies. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/developer-resources/","title":"Amazon Glacier Resources"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/cli/latest/reference/glacier/index.html","title":"Amazon Glacier - CLI Resources"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/aws-properties-s3-bucket.html","title":"Amazon Glacier in CloudFormation"}],"answers":[{"id":"5e40757e0ff52b4597ed3d7dae5905a2","text":"The RESTful Glacier web service","correct":true},{"id":"89dcebe9882f4d2a6ea3c2ca0cbb145e","text":"The AWS CLI","correct":true},{"id":"3e0049528ad7f75cce804b2f42daf046","text":"CloudFormation templates","correct":false},{"id":"e3153137238990b012fd6a2885e6793b","text":"The Java or .NET SDKs","correct":true},{"id":"64508034a3d69411b8f69baa321fe661","text":"Amazon S3 Lifecycle Policies","correct":true}]},{"id":"2srflb2w-gpba-wyok-a3ts-v64r4v1vd57h","domain":"tech","question":"You use containers to host your microservices, and you need to route traffic to those applications using a single load balancer. Which of the following services should you use to accomplish this?","explanation":"This routing can be done only with an Application Load Balancer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/details/#details","title":"About the ALB"}],"answers":[{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"7be6a0f173a965818e92c1df46c6626e","text":"AWS CodeDeploy","correct":false},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":true}]},{"id":"f9bc3071-e017-426b-bb59-bebf2bb60194","domain":"billing","question":"You need an AWS support plan for your production workloads, but want to keep costs to a minimum. Which of the following plans should you choose?","explanation":"The Business Support plan is specifically designed for production workloads in AWS. On one end, Basic Support is included for all AWS customers, and Developer Support plan is best suited for experimenting or testing in AWS. On the other end, thereâ€™s the Enterprise Support plan, which is ideal for business and mission-critical workloads.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]},{"id":"16rz9iw6-s5av-nrg1-1gja-89cbrnwj8uco","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are storage services?","explanation":"VPC is a Networking service, and RDS is a Database service, leaving S3 and Elastic File System as the storage services","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/efs/","title":"About EFS"}],"answers":[{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"1dbd7e466350bb810a3ea48be7668773","text":"AWS Elastic File System","correct":true},{"id":"6e11595bc7ccdbf672fefaababf72939","text":"AWS RDS","correct":false},{"id":"94a6c127c422f3501ac2fd0084ebbd25","text":"AWS VPC","correct":false}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true},{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true},{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true},{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false}]},{"id":"evaz1xrv-t8dc-4b8o-0z8b-k29mzh203trs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers the assistance of a Technical Account Manager?","explanation":"Only Enterprise (the highest level of Support Plan) offers the services of a Technical Account Manager.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"8d5e7e72f12067991186cdf3cb7d5d9d","text":"Premium","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false}]},{"id":"ipqdbu85-0egr-7f6l-daqk-ftz6657spa8l","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that is always online â€” without the need for human intervention?","explanation":"A highly available system is one that is always online â€” without the need for human intervention. Although Fault Tolerance is closely related to High Availability, FT usually implies a degradation of service without human intervention, unlike HA which is like-for-like.","links":[{"url":"https://media.amazonwebservices.com/architecturecenter/AWS_ac_ra_ftha_04.pdf","title":"Fault Tolerance and High Availability Infographic"}],"answers":[{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"35d7975974b40518da5e7f990c6a7d1d","text":"Fault Tolerant","correct":false},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":true},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false}]},{"id":"e64254c2-1a50-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services, which includes Amazon VPC. By comparison, the customer is responsible for what goes in the AWS Cloud. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses), security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic), and network ACLs as additional layers of security.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"97fd1873341a4d886cd8a23614cef0ff","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Service","correct":false},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"3ca98dadd6a9bcbe75450331cd449df5","text":"Network access control lists (network ACLs)","correct":true}]},{"id":"mlqp7x88-xfgl-3xkm-trto-wx59uhf7dox6","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below allows you to restrict access to individual objects in an S3 bucket? ","explanation":"Access Control Lists let you control access to individual objects within an S3 bucket, whereas Bucket Policies allow you to control access to entire buckets. In relation to S3, Bucket Control Lists and Access Policies do not exist as configuration items.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/using-iam-policies.html","title":"About S3 Bucket Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"7cfde5ee620a2532233ca18a68fd35ba","text":"Bucket Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"8eaf761b0344c54cfcf063cb006e4ad1","text":"Access Policies","correct":false},{"id":"64d03326bddfa39f7ae9a129e8b731c6","text":"Bucket Access Lists","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":true}]},{"id":"075e3cda-4e62-4381-bb3f-0cd061c73bb3","domain":"security","question":"A purchasing department staff member is setup as an AWS user in the companyâ€™s procurement AWS account. At each month-end, the staff member needs access to an application running on EC2 in the companyâ€™s accounts payable AWS account to reconcile reports. Which of the following provides the most secure and operationally efficient way to give the staff member access to the accounts payable application?","explanation":"The staff member should be given the ability to assume a role programmatically with the permissions necessary to run the accounts payable application. Setting up another AWS user for the staff member in the accounts payable account will require the presentation of hard credentials programmatically. Both federation and Lambda will require the use of a role as well, but with the added overhead of maintaining Active Directory or the Lambda function.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_common-scenarios.html","title":"Common Scenarios for Roles: Users, Applications, and Services"}],"answers":[{"id":"00383ff55511da79680a3cfdf7bd7a1b","text":"Configure Active Directory integration so that you can federate the staff memberâ€™s access to the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"e9c43624dba6130e04955aabf167b8b2","text":"Have the user request temporary security credentials for the application by assuming a role","correct":true},{"id":"926f9b540e5d5ff596976f059a7c9cbf","text":"Create a user for the staff member in the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"ecd3e317cda9a34ab820e6d6ff70fcf5","text":"Invoke an AWS Lambda function to run the application in the accounts payable AWS account","correct":false}]},{"id":"561b98dd-beb4-4111-8cb8-b5609a124873","domain":"tech","question":"What benefits can CloudFront bring to your e-commerce website?","explanation":"CloudFront provides the ability to cache both static and dynamic content in 200 points of presence located around the world, ensuring quick response times can be had by customers when retrieving cached website content. This inclueds protections with AWS WAF and AWS Shield. No additional analytics will necessarily be available, nor is CloudFront a database solution","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/features/","title":"Amazon CloudFront Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"6c47d5971e79af6daf2b24070bd1e8ac","text":"Scalable managed database which integrates seamlessly with Lambda and EC2","correct":false},{"id":"286fe6e5d97e4ad18aac77cef2b5e28c","text":"Increased application availability","correct":true},{"id":"3559eb841146fbbde9ede18594e319f1","text":"Protection against network and application layer attacks via WAF","correct":true},{"id":"61c592ef1e234bfa1834570f2238d22f","text":"Advanced analytics into customer journeys","correct":false},{"id":"bb42b85b5fcfff06d034f3102a1daa9e","text":"Lower latency for customers of your e-commerce website","correct":true}]},{"id":"4uvrqex2-fb79-fccq-6ogx-umyvygaxn7fi","domain":"security","question":"You are using your corporate directory to grant your users access to AWS services. What is this called?","explanation":"Federated Access is when you use an external directory, such as your coroporate one, to grant users in that directory access to AWS resources. Role-based and User group are more used to definied which resources a user is able to access once they have access, not the method by which they gain that access. Multifactor Authentication Access is the concept of a user requiring 2 secrets to be able to access the resources - usually their password and a 1 time code provided by a device under their control (e.g. a mobile phone).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/identity/federation/","title":"Identity Federation"}],"answers":[{"id":"d3973accf5dd88240811572d5f2608eb","text":"Multifactor Authentication Access","correct":false},{"id":"acce53b09f08060687cd88c30bce9db8","text":"Role-based Access","correct":false},{"id":"0db642c28b60c6a51547c3da2262902b","text":"User Group Access","correct":false},{"id":"00347e1d2de42be9910e334d04fe60dc","text":"Federated Access","correct":true}]},{"id":"b04194cb-7c18-41fd-af07-af547fcdf3df","domain":"security","question":"A consulting firm is conducting a Sarbanes-Oxley compliance audit of your IT operations. The auditor requests visibility to logs of event history across your AWS-based employee expense system infrastructure. Which AWS service will record and provide give you the information you need?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail provides visibility to API call activity for AWS infrastructure and other services. AWS Cloudwatch Logs might be part of a centralized logging solution, but all API event information will come from CloudTrail. AWS Systems Manager can process EC2 logs only, and AWS Compliance Manager is not a service offered by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/?nc2=h_m1","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"28408acf54ab04fe847fd24957e528d9","text":"AWS CloudWatch Logs","correct":false},{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"26ca9b29af36f84c577a85a80a58a381","text":"AWS CloudTrail","correct":true},{"id":"811708e04896b95951b61e58635cc92d","text":"AWS Compliance Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"e4306810-2a64-4eb4-9c58-431ea8a91190","domain":"tech","question":"A software development team needs to create numerous testing environments each day based on multiple concurrent project activities. Provisioning of these environments needs to happen within minutes to ensure that project deadlines are met. The number of environments needed daily varies depending shifting priorities in business requirements. How can the team best achieve the agility they need for creating the testing environments?","explanation":"AWS CloudFormation provides templates to specify all the AWS resources needed by the testing environments. These templates can be instantiated as stacks to provision consistent environments every time one is needed. AWS Auto Scaling will only handle the EC2 instances, and expands and contracts instances based on policies. AWS Systems Manager is useful for system administration tasks, and AWS Lambda has run-time limitations.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudformation/","title":"AWS CloudFormation"}],"answers":[{"id":"d9a6df6805662c26de87001a1d7b5ae4","text":"Use AWS Systems Manager Automation to provision and de-provision the testing environments","correct":false},{"id":"d0251c104fe180cf808a23905d11ab7c","text":"Leverage AWS Auto Scaling to expand and contract the testing server pool based on demand","correct":false},{"id":"5a6510861bc8f77b0a75412925312eff","text":"Invoke AWS Lambda functions to run the test scenarios","correct":false},{"id":"7eab42e9ed95a6b8f6eba51c1d6ba41e","text":"Have AWS CloudFormation provision the stacks and resources needed for the testing environments","correct":true}]},{"id":"11cddf60-2bb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is an example of Platform as a Service?","explanation":"Platform as a Service, or PaaS, enables the development, running, and management of applications on the cloud without the need to build and maintain any infrastructure. That is precisely what Elastic Beanstalk provides; the ability to quickly deploy and manage applications in the AWS Cloud without worrying about the infrastructure that runs those applications. Elastic Beanstalk is the only PaaS listed here.","links":[{"url":"https: //aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"bcf6eb183b7da148701bcc059a34675f","text":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"dee7ff8f7b10b9d388c7c561e9413b0d","text":"AWS Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"zb4ly2e6-g248-o6q2-ydke-pk8x90w6a03l","domain":"tech","question":"You have a variable and intermittent workload, so you want to use a compute service that allows you to pay only for the compute resources you use , without paying for compute time when your code isnâ€™t running. Which of the following services should you use?","explanation":"Lambda allows you to run a variable and intermittent code without paying for compute time when your code isnâ€™t running.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"c8f63ecaff5e983a2441126a241c4cfa","text":"ECS","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"ybx4uf1a-l9y3-aucn-tt1m-ku92d3hu5y5v","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are configuratble components of IAM?","explanation":"Users, Groups, Roles, and Permissions are integral to IAM. Authentication and Authorization are functions that IAM provides, but not actual components of it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/getting-started/","title":"IAM - Getting Started"}],"answers":[{"id":"3948d67c633d9035eaf2216ba0e1b2dc","text":"Authenticator","correct":false},{"id":"d08ccf52b4cdd08e41cfb99ec42e0b29","text":"Permissions","correct":true},{"id":"18ade94f5fe966167a6645362290cdcb","text":"Authorizer","correct":false},{"id":"a37ede293936e29279ed543129451ec3","text":"Groups","correct":true},{"id":"a5cd3ed116608dac017f14c046ea56bf","text":"Roles","correct":true},{"id":"f9aae5fda8d810a29f12d1e61b4ab25f","text":"Users","correct":true},{"id":"2999b7d01e6b02e94fc22c79b978d3b0","text":"Access controls","correct":false}]},{"id":"ij3guy5r-65pf-5sad-nyrn-vkpusbdxd3cz","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services can assist you with cost optimization?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor can assist you with the cost optimization of your AWS environment.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"065786b4-2fbf-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is an advantage of using Amazon Aurora over MySQL and PostgreSQL?","explanation":"Aurora, which is Amazonâ€™s very own relational database service (RDS) offering, is capable of delivering up to five times the throughput of MySQL and up to three times the throughput of PostgreSQL, therefore it is a faster RDS engine than MySQL and PostgresSQL. The other responses are not correct because all three database engines are supported in AWS RDS, provide high availability, and can auto-scale their storage capabilities.","links":[{"url":" https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What Is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"2af45970d86937f0ee6307f5f1d7f1e8","text":"Aurora is faster than MySQL and PostgreSQL.","correct":true},{"id":"b0e9556359058a92983935d53f8dd9ac","text":" Unlike MySQL and PostgreSQL, Aurora can be used with AWS Relational Database Service (RDS).","correct":false},{"id":"69b1cc807abf4ac85af0b5fd99275f27","text":"Unlike MySQL and PostgresSQL, Aurora can auto-scale in storage.","correct":false},{"id":"fe74accc7d3b87bf524b103b8501463c","text":"Unlike MySQL and PostgreSQL, Aurora is highly available.","correct":false}]},{"id":"719cc66e-ayev-f5lb-zoet-xaar4i1a3kub","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following EC2 options is best for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns?","explanation":"Reserved instances are the most economical option for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns - in this consumption method, you commit to using resources for a period of time for a reduced cost. On-Demand is great for when you don't have predictable patterns as you only pay for when you are using the resources. Spot works when your workload is interruptible and doesn't need to be available all the time.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/","title":"Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances"}],"answers":[{"id":"bad26119751b8bdb0b46bff9a096f500","text":"On-Demand instances","correct":false},{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false},{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true},{"id":"ead2a4026c18cbaca9c93c0974c23f89","text":"Dedicated Host","correct":false}]},{"id":"7gpfi6zh-od3t-hgmy-7puh-d955spmckv2u","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound cloud design?","explanation":"Build your systems to be scalable, use disposable resources, reduce infrastructure to code, and, please, assume EVERYTHING will fail sooner or later. Servers should be treated like cattle, where the exist to serve a function, and for a generally limited period of time, as opposed to pets which are kept and cared for over very long periods of time. There is no reason to limit the number of 3rd party services, if it makes the most sense in the case of the design at hand. Tightly-coupled components result in hard dependencies between different services, and usually lead to issues with either an applications health, or its scalability.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"c4feabf8a0fd67917d77220d3b036291","text":"Tightly-coupled components","correct":false},{"id":"af41549605744cf23f27cbc14458bf82","text":"Infrastructure as code","correct":true},{"id":"df89f307a97b6ecf5647735dcd89f7c8","text":"Limit the number of 3rd-party services.","correct":false},{"id":"31ae780d15d60c68f6689a039e6f3802","text":"Assume *everything* will fail.","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"9cb4d987bd4d50912c60823480c86972","text":"Treat your servers like pets, not cattle.","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"0b2dkrmk-derf-tm5u-h127-w4yffwtldij2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are Support Levels offered by AWS?","explanation":"AWS Support has four levels. Basic is their free entitlement for all AWS Customers. The three paid support plans in order of ascending cost are Developer, Business, and Enterprise. Start-up and Individual do not exist as Support Plans","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":true},{"id":"3263b7364a2b2cb3d4697003ef512748","text":"Start-up","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]},{"id":"19ddf237-f79d-4d25-b0ae-81419166300b","domain":"security","question":"Enabling Amazon GuardDuty automatically grants this service the permission to analyze which of the following data sources?","explanation":"Amazon GuardDuty monitors the security of your AWS environment by analyzing and processing three data sources, which are VPC Flow Logs, AWS CloudTrail event logs, and DNS logs.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/guardduty/latest/ug/what-is-guardduty.html","title":"What is GuardDuty?"}],"answers":[{"id":"da9b46af667cf2279d002b955813bb34","text":"AWS CloudTrail logs","correct":true},{"id":"6b7cef11406f2fff58dcc619a2b7e482","text":"Amazon S3 buckets","correct":false},{"id":"8db8c2b0bbd0ff71d1d15bb32f69e3b8","text":"VPC Flow Logs","correct":true},{"id":"a70a14359eb44629c70e41470e05570f","text":"DNS query logs","correct":true}]},{"id":"90df786a-99f7-45c0-b4ed-126bfc6c55de","domain":"concepts","question":"A mobile shopping list app needs to be able to add, delete, and update items on specific lists anytime a user desires. The backend for the app will run on Amazon EC2 instances with Auto Scaling to manage fluctuations in user demand. Many times, a user will perform maintenance on many list items in a single session. What design characteristic must be incorporated into the app for these requirements to be met?","explanation":"In order for horizontal scaling to be effective, you'll want to make sure the app doesn't store previous transaction or session information on specific EC2 instances. That way, any EC2 instance provisioned by Auto Scaling can process the request. Leveraging load balancing is also a good practice, but doesn't address the need for a stateless app. Session affinity goes the other direction, directing a load balancer to route transactions to a specific instance each time. Bootstrapping runs scripts each time an EC2 instance is provisioned.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud - AWS Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"712738cb3dbc4b4aeb218af7b44b731c","text":"Use bootstrapping on the EC2 instances","correct":false},{"id":"7f3d1559e229505103abfd9297d2249c","text":"Make sure the app doesnâ€™t need knowledge of previous transactions","correct":true},{"id":"175dc87c438249634b2c6104864a2e6a","text":"Leverage load balancing to distribute transactions to multiple nodes","correct":false},{"id":"3169165ef00c3474aa673628039e0dc1","text":"Implement session affinity","correct":false}]},{"id":"pylft010-qst0-1uhz-wkp8-iok6z6z5m9zs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are payment options for Reserved Instances?","explanation":"Reserves instances are available with all upfront, partial upfront, or no upfront (AURI, PURI, and NURI) pricing.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"38cf9fac137f64bb80e2a3a31163f746","text":"DURI","correct":false},{"id":"283f03b472e12ba313511c7fbd4bcd9c","text":"AURI","correct":true},{"id":"592425dc8e5fd4ddddb711fcb56dcd41","text":"MURI","correct":false},{"id":"19eeb11e145e7494345b431a13df9b60","text":"PURI","correct":true},{"id":"53ed2947db4516ed0087c215e7ffc748","text":"NURI","correct":true}]},{"id":"trwylx1o-zl9g-9de6-rxeg-gp4pakkifop1","domain":"tech","question":"The load on your application fluctuates by day of the week. Wednesdays have the most traffic; Saturdays have the least traffic. Which AWS service allows you to ensure you have the correct amount of compute capacity while also optimizing on a cost basis? ","explanation":"Auto Scaling allows you to add or remove EC2 instances based on conditions you specify. Auto-Scaling events can be scheduled to meet predictable changes in the load on your application.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"afd14eb3f151c84e6ef7ab63812b4fbc","text":"Auto Scaling","correct":true},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"a2c64f657687c46ed9811761849051e4","text":"EC2 Container Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"2df4774c-2e69-4156-96c5-b1efbfba754f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. This means there will always be more AZs than Regions. Edge locations are separate from AZs and Regions, and there are more Edge Locations than Regions and Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"f35fa3c5e765907efd6efa66bc1741c3","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"f4b49cc5b3d286cd78cac99f03cecce3","text":"There are more Regions than Availability zones","correct":false},{"id":"26c658a3c4aee0122f0178a65f0ea80b","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Regions","correct":true},{"id":"29030db1d3f86fea8d8779a9c964c207","text":"There are more Availability Zones than Edge locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"c6jepoji-nqyo-0t96-juj8-ob2lymloevj9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Assurance Program?","explanation":"Certifications/Attestations and Compliance with Laws and Regulations are cornerstones of the of the AWS Assurance Program.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Assurance"}],"answers":[{"id":"de208db5a32df9befe2ed7f080863f9e","text":"Customer Testimonials","correct":false},{"id":"506afacef0a47cc7635b5cf0a3476c31","text":"Certifications/Attestations","correct":true},{"id":"fc0d934854b825185d4ea2079edf68c3","text":"Compliance with Laws and Regulations","correct":true},{"id":"4dc626268903b46b79d0a76e0a989cf8","text":"Partner Validations","correct":false},{"id":"19d78b92947f957cca4c7698118fdb82","text":"Following industry best practices","correct":false}]},{"id":"4hjaxq6n-z5w0-zfz5-rhia-l14kd19r6656","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are best practices when it comes to securing your AWS account?","explanation":"Creating individual IAM users, using groups to assign them permission and creating a strong password policy are all key components of securing your AWS account. The root user should only be used in emergencies, therefore there should be no need to have Root Access Keys which allow the root user Programmatic access - any Programmatic access should use something other than the root account. It is not possible to delete the root password, and this should be securely, safely stored and not used in any applications!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"9c2eddf5402bf5f69b4cfd6f6cbb82ef","text":"Store your Root account keys on your application for easy access.","correct":false},{"id":"af5257e2e32921faab688050c9de091e","text":"Apply an IAM password policy.","correct":true},{"id":"07623cbc5a5f07bde8c94a98256a165f","text":"Use groups to assign permissions.","correct":true},{"id":"5d44464e3d76ef6a6641b8044d7d2525","text":"Activate MFA on the Root Account.","correct":true},{"id":"561f3fa869736d8c37dd07fc1284f00f","text":"Delete your Root access keys.","correct":true},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"427d69ad60aa7d9c68a9214e103fc80a","text":"Delete your Root account password.","correct":false}]},{"id":"a1113592-8add-4bc5-bc72-07b4af069ecb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following enables customers to find, test, and buy software from independent vendors to run on AWS?","explanation":"AWS Marketplace is the place to get software that runs on AWS. Amazon Connect is a cloud-based contact center; AWS Cost Explorer is for evaluating your account costs and usage, and AWS Budgets is for budgeting costs and usage.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/marketplace","title":"AWS Marketplace"}],"answers":[{"id":"c7f176d72688fd87853e31b84159d541","text":"AWS Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"cab27dc53edb571cac663ce2e16450dc","text":"AWS Marketplace","correct":true},{"id":"3597dfc4f30310d82a68c84b2c82e1a8","text":"Amazon Connect","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true},{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false}]},{"id":"123bb9de-8d93-4feb-81c0-d4e85038cd47","domain":"tech","question":"When setting up the properties of an S3 bucket, which of the following options should you select to get detailed records for the requests made to the bucket?","explanation":"Server access logging is what you should select to record and get information on the requests made to your bucket. Object-level logging, sometimes referred to as S3 CloudTrail logging, saves all API events performed on the S3 bucket in json format.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/ServerLogs.html","title":"Amazon S3 Server Access Logging"}],"answers":[{"id":"f87d839acefa86eff3c90b1b44be4aba","text":"Object-level logging","correct":false},{"id":"189f63f277cd73395561651753563065","text":"Tags","correct":false},{"id":"198a30920479d1d8e2509b9b59f3d700","text":"Versioning","correct":false},{"id":"30054ccc9b587d53668a89942396874c","text":"Server access logging","correct":true}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they donâ€™t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false},{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false},{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false},{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true}]},{"id":"ej2zjxm0-a6xk-q2af-mol8-3c9zwje8qxyh","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans features a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system?","explanation":"Both the Business and Enterprise support levels offer a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system. Developer is < 12-hour response time in case of any system impairment. Basic does not offer any support for system impairment. Individual is not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false}]},{"id":"lzz1xk7l-o7hw-05ld-eq4w-bnnsryn338qb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below can be specified as an origin when creating a CloudFront distribution?","explanation":"A CloudFront Origin can be an S3 bucket, an Elastic Load Balancer, or a valid domain name.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/DownloadDistS3AndCustomOrigins.html","title":"CloudFront Origins"}],"answers":[{"id":"9cf4bd30d8e419d4586659b785653daf","text":"An S3 Bucket","correct":true},{"id":"c0289d18d5fb07085b2755204da9008b","text":"A domain name","correct":true},{"id":"c727fd87c3ae231f10b00f5df6719fdc","text":"An RDS instance","correct":false},{"id":"19c648650c3e65663a1edebcca84f065","text":"An ELB","correct":true}]},{"id":"npfixa13-rww8-6ifs-mar3-1z12ny6vwzat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following services will help you optimize your entire AWS environment in real-time following AWS best practices?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor helps you optimize your entire AWS environment in real-time following AWS best practices. It helps you optimize cost, fault-tolerance, and more.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true}]},{"id":"79925710-1b09-449b-8a8f-51ebb4ae011f","domain":"security","question":"You are setting up an S3 bucket to host a public website. You have uploaded the files for your website to S3 but when clicking on the object url of the file to verify it can be seen you receive the message access denied, you have tried making the file public but the option is not available. What configuration has been missed?","explanation":"To enable the option for selecting an object to be public you first need to disable the Block Public Access setting on the S3 bucket. This setting is in place to prevent accidental configuration of the S3 bucket and objects being visible from anywhere on the internet.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/WebsiteHosting.html","title":"Hosting a Static Website on Amazon S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"0781b9f1fa104477da535d137bd67124","text":"Removing Block Public Access from the bucket","correct":true},{"id":"dc91d7c1f9dfd359ce1f57aa8b2eebb9","text":"The IAM user for S3 Public Website Hosting is currently disabled","correct":false},{"id":"f84968f028b1b306769936b96c99902e","text":"Creating and linking an S3 IAM role to your S3 bucket","correct":false},{"id":"2e12d1999c3eb36bf65cfca4200e4a59","text":"Adding a CNAME value to Route53 for the website","correct":false}]},{"id":"su6exaen-uvfq-awbs-r1m3-y06rtjhsbaw6","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services can help you assess the fault-tolerance of your AWS environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor can help you assess the fault-tolerance of your AWS environment. AWS Inspector can help you assess your security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"b9e84187-a101-b202-89a5-c5882d80f712","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Patch Management is a Shared Control, since AWS is responsible for patching and fixing flaws within the infrastructure, including managed services like RDS, but customers are responsible for patching their guest OS and applications. Firmware Upgrades, and other Hardware maintenance processes are solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of Security Groups remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"9ce46290f3196adff1535137f5fc1ee9","text":"Firmware Upgrades","correct":false},{"id":"5d8e5aef41d3dab7bda43eaace3a2a06","text":"Patch Management","correct":true},{"id":"474eabe8590389108f1fc92c9435c405","text":"Security Group Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"c57c1a92dac4991db4fa1bca1517cca0","text":"Hardware Maintanence","correct":false}]},{"id":"8ilibd7u-7ml9-492r-etu0-n4zubf409ykt","domain":"tech","question":"Amazon Lightsail is an example of which of the following?","explanation":"Lightsail is AWS' Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) offering - this means that when using Lightsail you don't need to worry about all the components that are required to deliver the Instance such as storage, data, and instance size as AWS manages all that for you. Amazon Lightsail takes away many of the complexities of managing an Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) solution, like some of the networking. This can also be a drawback, if you want to have a highly configurable service. Since Lightsail lets you run a variety of fully-features applications, it is neither a Software as a Service (SaaS), nor Function as a Service (FaaS) offering ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/","title":"About Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"68c0c53c6a8ab47f4b611dbf1c347a26","text":"Software as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"f53d5c67ce1a2058f77a32af9a7d0c66","text":"Functions as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"0fdc9e547679a07630645143e79cce26","text":"Infrastructure as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"8f637a063500ec391f887ff70bda5f30","text":"Platform as a Service","correct":true}]},{"id":"5fd1imv7-lqes-7e9n-vz33-eau71532v2ly","domain":"security","question":"How does AWS Shield Standard help protect your environment?","explanation":"AWS Shield Standard is included at no extra cost but will only block DDOS attacks on your AWS resources - it will not scan the contents of incoming or outgoing traffic (this is a function of WAF) and will not protect your environment from viruses","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/shield-chapter.html","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"55063c26653acc06bd00cc13e1acc3a4","text":"By scanning your instances for viruses","correct":false},{"id":"3e6fc5c29a49e9d5c54bd4950ad5cbe0","text":"By scanning outgoing application traffic for sensitive information","correct":false},{"id":"84009024e233c4995b00c514474f0ae5","text":"By Blocking DDOS attacks","correct":true},{"id":"b1d6309ddb9cc2f856af5a3bab83f37e","text":"By scanning incoming application traffic for know attacks","correct":false}]},{"id":"2b40d035-75be-4cc9-8fd2-f68278e78e0c","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following services does the AWS Shield Standard plan provide?","explanation":"AWS Shield safeguards web applications. AWS Shield Standard is a base-level plan with features that include network flow monitoring and assistance with protection from common DDoS attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/ddos-overview.html","title":"How AWS Shield Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"3a79a8da690d2e99e95cddb10910920d","text":"Reimburse related Route 53, CloudFront, and ELB DDoS charges","correct":false},{"id":"081cd9acf98f7578f0580361186fb8e9","text":"Network flow monitoring","correct":true},{"id":"00374233c3440bca78e09204f226ada6","text":"Post-attack analysis","correct":false},{"id":"ced7f2b0843e775cca051172231e93db","text":"Assistance with protection from common DDoS attacks","correct":true}]},{"id":"9a62e30f-6366-4ba3-a6f9-29118a4432d8","domain":"billing","question":"When would you use the Reserved Instance pricing model?","explanation":"Reserved instances are a great way of reducing costs on long running applications with predictable workloads. Even if the money is not available to make upfront payments, using Reserved Instances over longer periods can still be useful for cost savings","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"f5bfd0de9a22ee48b87ae246ed4f4042","text":"CAPEX vs OPEX charging model","correct":true},{"id":"79c233b246a21fbcf2c865dcef7f0791","text":"Predictable workload types","correct":true},{"id":"e757909a259f51f248d287636899abda","text":"Ability to bid on the lowest compute price possible","correct":false},{"id":"642a643c75d27712431a1b79c28e8cc5","text":"Unpredictable workloads","correct":false}]},{"id":"2cp5w12s-zexu-46ts-0im3-vuthjxgjujs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used?","explanation":"Elasticity describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"fb76c61f626c7fb0fd2ee1226e9fd8bd","text":"Fault-tolerance","correct":false}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false},{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false}]},{"id":"a6f49f26-0fbc-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for Amazon RDS?","explanation":"You can pay for Amazon RDS using either On-Demand or Reserved instance pricing.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"6c9d6b8aea6f3d16847bdebe05878a2d","text":"Spot","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true},{"id":"bda9eb7fcdccf237f87fb190ee3b4275","text":"Dedicated Server","correct":false}]},{"id":"bcecb806-dc3d-42d5-abaf-92b78f78bf00","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to network security for an EC2 instance in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service. In this scenario, AWS is responsible for the underlying network hardware, not the customer. However the customer is responsible for ensuring that only wanted, valid traffic reaches their EC2 instance through the use of Security Groups, Access Control Lists or Software Firewalls","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"d06119c27ec0a4e3b321bd66da22fea2","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"1dbd0eb41e4e90508191eb1f5a99b615","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring unwanted traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"4aa6ca9653c0c4e24ff62399d1e4ca09","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"e61949c2c6f3b07d6b052aeed05cafd5","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring unwanted traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"01407b8624848ffc3a63fcbb919421fb","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not impair the network hardware","correct":true},{"id":"3bab15fdca03e0fc9fcb17e344d1ffed","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not impair the network hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"riqpy09p-2mos-4v71-m59a-je7iknttb5c4","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following is generally not billed for on the AWS platform?","explanation":"Data Transferred in to AWS is almost always free of charge (excluding large transfer services, like AWS Snowball). The reason for this, and best way to remember it is that AWS don't mind you transferring lots of data in to their services, since you'll already be paying to use and store it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"a5227beaedc6d59181cd9199f25d32ce","text":"Data-out","correct":false},{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false},{"id":"8c4aa541ee911e8d80451ef8cc304806","text":"Storage","correct":false},{"id":"72a2694d2bcec74cfbc3e76e2e8d6c24","text":"Data-in","correct":true}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false}]},{"id":"6c02ad88-1feb-11ea-a32c-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon DynamoDB storage will you get?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 25 GB of DynamoDB storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"dcfebc6fbca2c5316f55c914e6593d2d","text":"100 GB","correct":false},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"272aa49fa956677af70625391009423f","text":"25 GB","correct":true},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false}]},{"id":"yhwuezmk-vte7-c3ty-x612-wvd1qi3aw2us","domain":"tech","question":"Youâ€™ve been tasked with assessing your AWS infrastructure in terms of cost optimization. Which of the following AWS services would help with this task? ","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor is an online tool that provides you with real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"ee58e6973ab1b8a94d5434399ac85129","text":"Cloud Trail","correct":false},{"id":"bd02384ebb7e76c74ae044ad5cf295c1","text":" AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The companyâ€™s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the companyâ€™s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false},{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false}]},{"id":"ism9fl1z-nho7-nn22-5sn8-4qqdyyu4pyeq","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWSâ€™ event-driven, serverless compute service?","explanation":"Lambda is AWSâ€™ event-driven, serverless compute service that allows you to run code without having to deploy or manage any of the underlying resources such as EC2 instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"o8aqfsp4-kk6k-gyj7-frq7-4bpn7iv5zqm8","domain":"concepts","question":"You have a mission-critical application which must be globally available at all times. Which deployment strategy should you follow?","explanation":"A Multi-Region deployment will best ensure global availability. While it can be the most expensive, and complex to configure, Multi-Regional architectures will ensure that even if all Availability Zones in a single region fail due to a catastrophic event, your data will remain accessible.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"91d7ff212b9bda483701aeb4209ae5ec","text":"Deploy to all Availability Zones in your home region.","correct":false},{"id":"86b2c5243e03e210528f020bad4efdb9","text":"Multi-VPC in two AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"ec206762c0bea997a5b0f91783cce54f","text":"Multi-Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"e4ec2833a31f482abfdb31691f0351dc","text":"Multi-Region","correct":true}]},{"id":"8d9bfa67-4685-4ba8-a5a7-d0518daba638","domain":"billing","question":"If you want access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks, which of these support plans will provide that?","explanation":"You must choose either the Business or Enterprise support plan to gain access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true}]}]}}}}
